Ximena IX, D.
Damn it!
He's tough...
If I can slow him down, then
one second's all I need…
Kirito!
if only i had my scope i get it
now there are things i shouldn't
forget what it means to kill the
significance of taking life and once i
accept it maybe then i'll be able to
find some closure that's how i see
it right now kirito's trying to get
that closure he was talking about
he's confronting his demons
from sao by taking on the person
who represents them death gun and
the reason he can isn't because
he's strong it's because he
accepts what he did even though it
still tears him up and he's still
trying to move on despite it
I gotta do something
gentle to see the future I
will be happy to see the world
I will be happy to see the
world I will be happy to see
the red eyes I will be happy
to see
the tears
I can't hear
the sound of the beginning,
but I can't hear the sound of
the sound of the beginning.
He's sweating so much.
He'll dehydrate soon.
I wonder if we can get him to log out.
Or at least warn him.
No, he wouldn't hear us.
The dive blocks everything out.
The Amu Sphere is designed
with stuff like this in mind,
so it should shut off if
he gets too dehydrated.
Okay then.
I guess we just have to wait.
Hey, Mommy.
Try holding Daddy's hand.
He'll feel the warmth of your touch
and know you're here watching over him.
Since I can't touch anything in
your world, hold it for me, too.
I know he won't feel me there, but still.
No, that's not true.
I'm sure he'll feel your hand, too.
I know he will.
We'll cheer him on, together.
Mommy.
Hang in there, Kirito.
Fight for what you believe in.
And I'll be right here by your side.
Wherever you go, and whatever
you do, I'll always be with you.
He's right.
I didn't want to know his name.
I didn't want anything to do with him.
But I should have known.
I wouldn't be rid of him that easy.
I didn't forget.
I only pretended to.
But I was just fooling myself.
Red eyes.
I saw them in the
briefing before the raid.
Black.
Red.
Zaza!
Red-Eyed Zaza! That's
you! That's your name!
Kidicho!
Xenon's distracting him
with her bullet line!
She's got him in her sights,
using all her skill and spirit
to keep it trained on him.
It's like a phantom bullet!
One last attack!
I can't waste this chance!
Oh, my God. No!
Fool.
It's not over yet.
You can't stop me.
He'll find you.
No, Zaza.
You're done.
And we'll find your partner too.
He won't kill anyone anymore.
Laughing Coffin's dead.
Kirito!
Daddy!
It's over.
Yeah.
I guess now, we should probably
get this tourney over with, huh?
Yeah, we should.
With Death Gun out of the picture,
I'm pretty sure the guy casing
out your apartment's taken off.
I don't think you'll be in
any danger when you log out.
But you should call the cops
when you do, just to be safe!
Okay, but what am I supposed to tell them?
Oh yeah, right.
The guy I work for is with the government.
I could ask him to send
the cops to your place?
But how am I going to get your info?
I can't really ask for it in here?
It's cool, I'll tell you. Huh?
Are you sure?
My name is Shino.
Shino Asura.
And I live here.
You're not going to believe this, but
you're close to the place I'm diving from.
Yeah?
Wow, no way.
How about this?
After we log out, I could head
over to you. You would? Really?
No, I'm good.
A friend of mine lives near me,
so I've got help if I need it.
Okay,
but after I log out, I'll call the guy
I work for and have him send the cops,
if you're cool with that.
Mm-hmm, sounds good.
But not good enough.
You just gonna log out
without telling me your info?
Oh, right, sorry.
My real name is Kazuto Kirigaya.
That's how you got Kirito?
Seriously?
Talk about a lack of imagination.
Yeah, well, like you're one to talk.
All right, then.
If we're ever going to log out of
this thing, we've got to end B .O .B.
first.
So, how do you want to do this?
You want to have a duel
like we did yesterday?
Hmm.
Look at yourself.
You're all banged up.
There's no challenge in beating someone
who's already as thrashed as you.
Nah, I'll take you on at the next B .O
.B., but you better not leave me hanging.
Ugh.
Well, let's get this
thing over with already.
How are we going to do that?
Unless one of our HPs drains out all the
way, there's not going to be a winner.
I guess you didn't hear what
happened in the first POB.
There were two winners.
The player who should have won
let his guard down too soon,
so his opponent gave him what
we call a souvenir grenade.
A souvenir grenade?
The heck's that? This.
No!
OKK adelante! Kishe?
ha, ha,
ha.
Death Gun had two victims this time.
That means he's got at least
two others helping him.
I don't know.
What am I doing?
Asura, you there?
It's me, Asura.
Shinkawa!
I just wanted to
congratulate you on your win.
I even brought some pastries.
Hey, congrats.
You were so awesome, Asura.
I mean, Sinon.
You did it.
You're the best gunner in GGO now.
I knew all along you could do it.
You deserve being number
one more than anybody.
You showed them all what
real strength's about.
You should be proud.
Thank you.
Um, Asada?
What's up?
You said, you said to wait.
Remember that?
What are you talking about?
Well, you told me to wait, and if
I did, then you'd be mine. Huh?
I waited.
I waited for you.
What's gotten into you?
From now on, I'll always be with you.
You don't need him to protect you.
That's my job.
I'm gonna protect you now.
Forever.
Shinkawa!
I love you, Asura.
You're mine.
My Asura.
Xenon. Mine.
Let go!
Why'd you push me away like that?
You made a promise.
We both did.
Shinkawa?
Don't make any sudden moves, Asada.
The syringe I'm holding's got a drug in it
that'll paralyze your
muscles in an instant.
Before you know it, your lungs
will stop thin your heart.
Syringe?
Maybe by injecting some
kind of drug or something?
That's one way.
Yeah, it is the family business.
I promised my dad I'd go to med
school, so it's a done deal.
Stuck with it now.
This is crazy.
You're the other Death Gun.
Ooh, I'm impressed.
You figured out Death Gun's little secret.
It's true.
I'm Death Gun's partner in crime.
Up to now, before this year's B .O .B.
anyway, I was the one playing Shterbin.
But today, I insisted on being
the one to do the job IRL.
Don't you see?
I had to be the one doing the deed.
I can't let some other guy touch
you, even if that guy's my brother.
Your brother?
So then, the player who belonged
to that murder guild and SAO,
that was your older brother.
Forget about him.
It's just you and me now, Asada.
Stop!
It's not too late.
You don't have to do this.
What about cram school, huh?
You said you were going to be a doctor.
Doctor?
You think I'd give a damn about that?
about my parents, those guys in school.
They're all assholes.
You know what would have made me happy?
To be the strongest player in GGO.
But that piece of shit Saxe lied
about AGI types being the strongest.
And I fell for it like an idiot!
You don't know.
GGO was everything to me.
And I gave everything up in the
real world for it, goddammit!
You killed Saxe.
Because he lied.
Oh, come on.
He was the perfect victim.
We had to show the world Death
Gun was the strongest in GGO.
In all the VR Miss.
What better person to
sacrifice than that dork?
And now that that's done, I
don't need this reality anymore.
Let's move on to the next one.
Come on, just you and me.
What are you saying?
We can go somewhere like GGO.
No. No.
Someplace with a fantasy vibe instead.
As long as it's with you, I don't care.
We'll be reborn.
Be husband and a wife.
We'll get a house.
We'll go on quests together.
Oh, and have kids, too.
It'll be so much fun.
I know I will.
Come with me.
Asuna.
You're so beautiful.
You are more than anything.
You're mine and no one else's.
I always loved you, Asuna. Always.
In school,
when I heard about what happened,
when I heard what you did,
I could look all over and never
find another girl like you.
I mean, you shot a real bad guy
with a real gun and killed him.
How cool is that?
I told you, didn't I?
I said you had real power.
Then I came up with the Death Gun Legend.
And I picked the Type 54
as his gun because of you.
That's how much I love you, Asuna.
I love you so much.
More than anything.
No.
I don't want to see anything
or feel anything anymore.
This isn't real.
It can't be.
Kirito, you went to all that trouble
to save me, but it was all for nothing.
How about this?
After we log out, I
could head over to you.
If he comes over, he'll be in danger.
And I can't do anything about it.
That's not true.
Up to this point, all we've been
doing was looking out for ourselves.
We certainly never fought for anyone else.
But now, even though it might be too late
for us, let's go fight for someone else.
Just this once, me and you.
Come on. Let's go.
I love you, Asuna.
Asuna!
No!
Let go of me! No!
Asuna! Asuna! Asuna! Asuna! Asuna!
Let's go!
Run, Xenon!
Kirito...
Once again, there's no one need to go.
I want to be stronger and stronger,
I want to be a dream.
I want to be a dream like this,
Next time, one little step.